Seiichi and the wounded Louise set off
from Barbador Magic Academy.
After they arrived,
the Wimberg Kingdom and the Demon Kingdom
successfully forged their alliance.
Meanwhile, back at Barbador Magic Academy,
Airin was acting somewhat suspiciously...
Guess it's about time.
This week, we're starting with what
happened at Barbador Magic Academy
shortly after Seiichi left
for the Wimberg Kingdom.
Seiichi-sensei, take care.
Well, time to head back to the cafeteria.
That's all you ever do, glutton.
All right, back to the classroom.
Time to head back.
I wish I could have gone with the boss man.
Time to eat more!
You still want to eat?
What's wrong? You're usually much more lively.
You think Sei-chan will be okay?
It's Seiichi-kun we're talking about.
Of course he'll be fine.
I hope you're right.
Well, I'm going back to the classroom.
Will everything really be all right, Sei-chan?
Without you here at the academy?
The Fruit of Evolution 2:
Before I Knew It, My Life Had It Made
Gempel the Doppelganger
I'm Gempel the Doppelganger.
The man who would one day be known as one
of the top four of the Great Devil Order.
Believe it or not, when I was a child,
I grew up as an upper-class noble
who didn't lack for anything.
But my heart never felt fulfilled.
I'd always realized it.
People weren't approaching me.
They were only after my status as a noble.
Even my parents didn't show me any love.
I was nothing more than a tool to
inherit and continue their lineage.
No one paid attention to my true face.
The moment I fell into despair over that
was the moment I lost my face.
Airin? What are you doing?
This is the men's bathroom.
One of Hiiragi Seiichi's students?
Perfect timing.
What are you doing here?
I came here to crush you two.
To make Sei-chan feel despair.
Sei-chan? You mean Seiichi-sensei?
Airin! What in the world is wrong with you?!
Here I go!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Doppelganger!
S-So bright!
This is what I'm doing!
S-Saria-san?
Transformation magic?
Baird's got you beat in terms of power.
I'm not so sure about that.
She transformed?!
Is that Airin's magic?!
Whoa, man, what's going on?
By the way, I can also copy their specs.
I didn't know Airin had
an ability like this.
I'm...
...not Airin!
My true identity is...
Gempel the Doppelganger, one of
the Great Devil Order's top four!
Gempel the Doppelganger
Well? Surprised, aren't you?
When Seiichi gets back,
I'll execute you before his eyes.
Hiiragi Seiichi.
I'll send everyone you
cherish to the afterlife.
Starting with...
A member of Hiiragi Seiichi's
army, Lulune the Donkey.
I'll bet he'll feel utter
despair when he loses
someone he's shared joys and sorrows with.
Your life is mine!
What?!
My food is mine!
I won't let anyone take it!
Huh? Food? I wasn't after that.
I was after your life!
Oh? Really?
Really.
Now that I look at you,
you're Airin, from my class, right?
This girl's an idiot!
Sorry for surprising you.
Don't worry about it.
So, why did you sneak up on me from behind?
Overlook that part!
Not good! Is she onto me?!
Are you...
hungry, by chance?
Huh?
O-Oh, yes, I am!
I see.
Then here's my favorite!
Bakudan!
Being hungry always makes you want
to attack from behind, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
You're the one who tried to save my master.
So have this as thanks.
Besides, it's nice to share food and
eat it together every now and then.
You're our friend, Airin.
I wouldn't normally do this for others.
You're special.
Friend...
Father, Mother.
Be quiet.
Today's meal is delicious.
I'm so glad I made it.
It's good.
But why are you giving this to me?
Huh?
Well, partly to thank you
for trying to save my master...
What? Is it stuck in your throat?
N-No, it's just my allergies.
But food also tastes better
when you eat with someone.
Now we're best friends!
Best friends?!
You dumbass!
Hey! Where are you going?!
I also have empyema!
I might have failed earlier,
but it won't go that way this time!
Oliga, I'll be taking your life.
Oliga-chan!
Oh, Glutton.
When she gets close, I'll snap her neck!
This girl?!
Here's an umbrella.
You didn't bring one, right?
You hold it, Lulune.
Since you're tall.
S-Sure.
It's an upper-class noble! Get him!
Hand over that damn umbrella!
Hey! Give it back!
Gempel, I heard your family
was stripped of its title.
All this time, you acted like
you were so much better than us!
Why are you giving me an umbrella?
You'll get all wet yourself.
I'm fine.
You may be a glutton,
but you're a good girl who's
always sharing food with me.
Besides, you're my buddy.
I'm her buddy?!
You dumbass!
Where are you going? You'll catch a cold.
Idiots don't catch colds!
I swear, every single one of them...
That's...
Artoria the Calamity.
This time, I won't fail.
I'll finish her for sure.
Doppelganger.
Using the man she loves the most,
Hiiragi Seiichi.
Continued in the second half.
I want to be through
the mountains by nightfall,
so let's deal with this quickly.
All right.
Then I'll go buy us some drinks.
Okay, thanks.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Are you hurt anywhere?
N-No, I was just recalling the past.
It's nothing.
I'm fine, young lady.
Saria!
I bought drinks, Seiichi.
Hey, have I seen him before?
I found him.
You're Seiichi-sensei from
Barbador Magic Academy, right?
How do you know me?
You're famous!
I heard you're so super strong that
the king of Wimberg relies on you!
Huh? Really?
Seiichi, you're amazing!
I heard you're a real hero!
What are you doing here all by yourself?
Me?
I'm on a journey.
Searching for fun things to do.
Wow, how nice!
We're on our way back now.
Hey...
Sensei, are you happy right now?
He is! Right, Seiichi?
Y-Yeah.
I'm jealous.
Huh? What'd you say?
Nothing. See you, Seiichi-sensei.
You're leaving?
It's okay.
We'll meet again for sure.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Ar!
S-Seiichi?
Why are you here?
What about Wimberg? What about Saria?
I came back all by myself
because I wanted to see you alone.
You're the only one I have
eyes for right now, Ar.
Wh-Where is this coming from?
Ar, may I hug you?
Wh-What are you saying?
S-Sei—
Got you.
What are you saying?!
What has gotten into you?!
Seiichi!
Seiichi, are you okay?!
Does this Seiichi guy go
through this all the time?
Sorry, it was force of habit!
B-But...
I really was worried about you back then.
I'm truly glad you came back to life.
I'm the one who brought
him back to life, though.
I told you before, right?
People call me the Calamity,
but you accepted everything
about me, and I'm grateful for that.
So I want to accept everything about you, too.
Everything...
No one pays attention to my
feelings, to my true face.
Why?
I-Isn't that obvious?
Because I—
You?
Because I love you!
L-L-L...
L-Love?
So, Seiichi, go ahead... and hug me!
Is Hiiragi Seiichi really such a good guy?!
H-Huh?
Don't ignore me!
Again?!
Why do they all adore
Hiiragi Seiichi so much?
I decided to spend some time
as Seiichi in order to find out.
Everyone did so well on their last quiz.
It's thanks to you, Sensei!
Oh, no, that's not true.
Thank you so much.
This is quite a feast!
It's nice to eat outdoors like this
every once in a while.
The air is nice, too.
Yeah! This air is yummy!
Lulune, you mean the sandwiches, not the air.
Naturally!
Not good!
I was planning to learn
why they adore Seiichi,
but I've started enjoying this school life!
So, Principal...
You wanted to discuss
something with us, didn't you?
Yes, actually.
It's about the Great Devil Order.
You did say that the day
of the final battle was close.
That's right.
What I want to talk to you about is...
What's this doing here?!
Hmph. It's probably a monster that was
awakened by the Great Devil's pulse.
This thing's strong!
Get away from it right now!
I'd love to, but...
Seiichi!
Onii-chan, you're amazing!
You're so reliable, Master!
That makes it clear.
To be honest, I've sensed an evil
presence here at the academy lately,
but I hadn't been able to locate it.
He's an assassin sent
by the Great Devil Order.
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
You don't look happy.
That's not true. I'm always with—
Hold it right there!
Kannazuki Karen? Why are you here?
You might be able to deceive their eyes,
but you can't deceive my nose!
That man isn't Seiichi-kun!
Onii-chan?
S-Seriously?
Do you... h-have any proof of that?
I have evidence!
Airin?
The one who approached Lulune
several days ago was a fake Airin.
I rescued the real one from
the academy's chicken coop.
Man, you really saved me from that one!
I don't know what happened,
but when I came to, I was with the chickens.
Even if you can copy his
appearance and abilities,
you can't copy Seiichi-kun's
fragrant body odor.
Then... who in the world are you?
Guess the cat's out of the bag now!
So bright!
I'm one of the Great Devil Order's top four,
Gempel the Doppelganger.
One of the Great Devil Order's top four?!
You're right.
I used the chaos of the fight
between Seiichi and the apostles
to swap places with that lady there.
Why would you do that?!
Because I want to capture you all
and eliminate you in front of Seiichi.
That's the best strategy for
plunging him into the pit of despair!
What?!
At least, that was the plan before
I became Seiichi and realized something.
I lived my entire life
without being loved by anyone,
so I never cared if anyone else died.
But now, I think I understand.
Losing the people precious
to you is a very sad thing.
That's why I couldn't help saving you all.
I'm such an idiot.
You...
From now on, I think I'll try to find
someone to accept me like Seiichi did.
Someone who will be fond of me.
At least, that's how I want to live.
Though I doubt I'll ever measure up to him.
Later.
You can do it.
I can smell that potential in you.
Thanks, lady with the keen nose.
Should we really just let him go?
With his power, it would be
a trivial matter to kill us all.
Yet he didn't do that.
So I want to believe in him.
I want to believe there's a ray of hope
for those who have made mistakes, as well.
Well, what should I do now?
You, huh?
Perfect timing.
I'm leaving the Great Devil Order.
I don't care about all this despair
and Great Devil stuff anymore.
So I'm going to find someone
to love, who'll love m—
That boy was cute, wasn't he?
Yeah, he was.
What's the matter?
Well...
I just feel like I've seen him
somewhere before.
Everyone, the battle against
the Great Devil Order is nigh!
So let's put our spirit into it!
Yeah!
Now, let's commence the operation.
A murderer is on the loose
in that crazy guild!
The victim is the pacifier man!
Wait, who's that?
Guscle and the others set out to resolve it,
but wait, will I get to show up at all?!
Next time: "Vitor the Resonance."
Next Time
Victor the Resonance
It's a sausage fest of perverted
gentlemen showing off!